man
I remember before I first started doing
comedy man I had equipment I didn't quit
my job I actually got fired from my job
because I went out on my job
um actually got a promotion on my job
one time and my boss wanted to go out to
to celebrate and cloudy if you ever
heard of this place he wanted to go out
and celebrate at a place called
um Soup Plantation have you ever heard
of that place
yes it's a place that serves uh soup and
it's called Soup Plantation
I'm not getting out the car I'm good
[Applause]
I don't feel comfortable
going into a place I don't want anything
to do with the word Plantation see this
this outfit is cotton-free
to do with the word Plantation what is
established 1865.
good is that a horse in the parking lot
seriously like you can tell it was no
minorities in that boardroom meeting
whatsoever right they couldn't call it
soup Town Soup City nothing we're gonna
call it Soup Plantation all right I
think we got one John so we can go home
high five all right
[Music]
I told him I wasn't getting out of the
car and he got mad at me right he got
mad he said man stop stop tripping stop
tripping they got so many different
suits you can pick from I like pick
[Applause]
Les
I'm gonna pick myself up about this job
that's what I'm gonna do
go in there
I don't know I can only imagine how that
Happy Birthday song goes in that place
they don't sing Happy Birthday whether
they do give your freedom or something
like that
so like I said earlier though I do have
three girls I do have two girls I have a
four-year-old her name is Kayla uh the
other day I went to the store with my
daughter uh I went to go buy some items
and Lucas they like to run to the toy
all right they want to pick up toys she
wants to pick up a Barbie doll I'm like
put that down I'm not buying any more
Barbie dolls because I always end up
with their heads missing no clothes on
all over the floor I'm not buying
thank you
I'm not buying it right
so I buy my items
I get my car
I'm 12 miles down the road right and I
happen to look in the back seat
and my daughter has the Barbie doll
in the back seat right and I'm like
um that kind of stuff so you Target
because I'm 12 miles down the road you
need to up the security game you got a
four-year-old get over here like that
you need your manuals you need to watch
everybody like
that's one for her um
foreign
part that we went back to that same
store like two weeks later and she tried
to pick up the same Barbie doll right
and then I had to finally set her down I
had to give her that talk right I had to
look at her in her eyes and I had to say
um
Kayla sweetheart yet you can't do that
you can't do that but here take these
Beat headphones by Dr Dre hold that
so those are three hundred dollars hold
that
stop crying you did this before stand up
straight you can do it
bite those tears away
foreign
hey thank you guys so much for watching
don't forget to download the dry bar
comedy app and use the promo code E.L
Smith